<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Overige Taken on Sips Joeri - Gip site</title>
    <link>http://joeri-sips.github.io/categories/overige-taken/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Overige Taken on Sips Joeri - Gip site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://joeri-sips.github.io/categories/overige-taken/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

    <item>
      <title>Database</title>
      <link>http://joeri-sips.github.io/taken/Database/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>http://joeri-sips.github.io/taken/Database/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Directory structuur en workflows</title>
      <link>http://joeri-sips.github.io/taken/WorkflowsCMS/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>http://joeri-sips.github.io/taken/WorkflowsCMS/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;hugo&#34; href=&#34;../../GipTaak09/index.html&#34; &gt;Webapplicatie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;directory-stuctuur:3fa7dd089e78336c36219b98ebf899f2&#34;&gt;Directory stuctuur&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;content:3fa7dd089e78336c36219b98ebf899f2&#34;&gt;content&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In de content map staan mijn posts verdeeld over 2 catgorieën: stagetaken en taken.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;layout:3fa7dd089e78336c36219b98ebf899f2&#34;&gt;layout&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hier staan de HTML files van de verschillende delen van mijn website.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;static:3fa7dd089e78336c36219b98ebf899f2&#34;&gt;static&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hierin vind je de css en de javascript bestanden voor de layout en de functionaliteit van de site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;config:3fa7dd089e78336c36219b98ebf899f2&#34;&gt;config&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hier kan je de tittel en de url van je site aanpassen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;workflows:3fa7dd089e78336c36219b98ebf899f2&#34;&gt;Workflows&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;de-start:3fa7dd089e78336c36219b98ebf899f2&#34;&gt;De start&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Om met Hugo te starten moet je een aantal dingen in orde brengen zoals je pad instellen en een paar lijntjes typen in de comandprompt, dit is al een struikelblok voor mensen die geen iformatica studeren of hebben gestudeerd.
Daar tegenover moet je om een Wordpress website te maken enkel de simpele stappen volgen die je worden opgelegd en je hebt geen andere software nodig. Maar net omdat het maken van een site met Wordpress zo gemakkelijk is
kan je het niet 100% personaliseren.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;posts:3fa7dd089e78336c36219b98ebf899f2&#34;&gt;Posts&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Op Hugo kan je vrijwel alles, alleen is er het probleem dat je moet weten hoe en bij de meeste dingen weet ik daarop het antwoord momenteel nog niet zoals: &amp;ldquo;hoe voeg je een afbeelding toe?&amp;rdquo;.
Eenmaal je uiteindelijk de basis van je hugo site hebt is het toevoegen van posts net zo gemakkelijk als op Wordpress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Na gewerkt te hebben met hugo zou ik liever gebruik maken van Wordpress omwille van de volgende redenen;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;het legt zichzelf uit,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;geen extra software nodig,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;vanaf dat je de website maakt staat hij al online.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>IT is life</title>
      <link>http://joeri-sips.github.io/taken/IT-autobiography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>http://joeri-sips.github.io/taken/IT-autobiography/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction:b8ba8b1fcf0c24f1bbf715390a897859&#34;&gt;Introduction:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My name is Joeri Sips, I am 17 years old and I’m an IT management student at the Immaculata institute in Oostmalle. In my free time I play a game called: “Destiny”in which I was the number one Belgian player last schoolyear but that’s no longer the case since I took a break from the game during the vacation and the other players caught up. And this is an autobiography about what IT was, is and will be in my life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;first-experiences:b8ba8b1fcf0c24f1bbf715390a897859&#34;&gt;First experiences:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think my interest in IT comes from my mother, she is working as a network manager nowadays.
That has been her work for as long as I can remember and longer; she even tells me stories of giving workshops on how to use a mouse. As I was learning mathematics when I was 7 years old, she made a program for me on which I had to solve multiplications and afterwards it checked my work and showed me if my answers were wrong or right. The first sites I used to visit were sites that had fun and small browsergames like Tetris variations or Pin Ball. I sometimes still visit one of those sites called “funnygames.nl” to play Warfare 1917 which used to be my favorite game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;it-now:b8ba8b1fcf0c24f1bbf715390a897859&#34;&gt;IT now:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two years ago I started playing a game called DUST 514 and it that game I met people from the USA, Sweden, Germany and South Africa who are still my friends today. At home I only use the computer 2 hours a day on average and only for school because at school we use them all the time. At home I use my Playstation and my mobile phone most of the time and a while ago my microphone for the playstation broke but I got my phone to work as mic which is cool right? Especially because no one I know knows how to do that except me. Last year I made a small browser game together with two friends and I see that as my biggest achievement thus far even though its just a “click game” and nothing too complicated. I’m just simply baffled with all you can do with IT and I like doing all you can do with it. That’s why I’m an IT student and because of that I’ve spent a lot of time with programs like Word and Excel and when I see other people use it I get nervous ifthey don’t use it in the most efficient and fast way. I like to call myself a power-user because a power-user is someone who knows all the shortcuts and the functionality of a computer and I match those qualities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;future-in-it:b8ba8b1fcf0c24f1bbf715390a897859&#34;&gt;Future in IT:&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the future I’d like to make a living of IT as a programmer and create things that will be used by a lot of people like games. Also I would like to get more hardware because I enjoy playing around with cables and seeing what I can do with different hardware and because boys sure like their toys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If IT wasn’t around now I’d probably be building camps and acting like I am a knight but because it is around it is a big part in my life; it wakes me up, it tells me what to do for school and it even finds me new friends .So I am thankful that I grew up recently and not 100 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://nl.tinypic.com?ref=208v521&#34; target=&#34;blank&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://i66.tinypic.com/208v521.jpg&#34; border=&#34;0&#34; alt=&#34;Image and video hosting by TinyPic&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>IT-profile</title>
      <link>http://joeri-sips.github.io/taken/IT-profile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>http://joeri-sips.github.io/taken/IT-profile/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hier een overzicht van &amp;ldquo;IT-skills&amp;rdquo; die ik op het immaculata instituut heb aangeleerd:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HTML:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;progress value=&#34;50&#34; max=&#34;100&#34;&gt;&lt;/progress&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CSS:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;progress value=&#34;70&#34; max=&#34;100&#34;&gt;&lt;/progress&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Javascript:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;progress value=&#34;65&#34; max=&#34;100&#34;&gt;&lt;/progress&gt;

&lt;p&gt;C#:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;progress value=&#34;60&#34; max=&#34;100&#34;&gt;&lt;/progress&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PHP:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;progress value=&#34;55&#34; max=&#34;100&#34;&gt;&lt;/progress&gt;
</description>
    </item>

    <item>
      <title>Javascript Applicatie</title>
      <link>http://joeri-sips.github.io/taken/JavascriptApp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>

      <guid>http://joeri-sips.github.io/taken/JavascriptApp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In mijn &lt;a class=&#34;hugo&#34; href=&#34;../../GipTaak09/index.html&#34; &gt;Webapplicatie&lt;/a&gt; ga je uit verschillende materialen telkens 1 kiezen en aan duiden of je het afkoelt of opwarmt waarop je het resultaat ziet. Vb. : Water, afkoelen = ijs. Dit wordt dan opgevrolijkt d.m.v. animaties en foto’s. Momenteel doe ik de animaties gewoon met de javascript library omdat dat momenteel al volstaat.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
